longer distance so you Kane has dialed in
at a six eight times magnification and
then all of a sudden you might shoot
maybe drove and then a pig comes in
like 180 in front of you and then you can then
angle it and you have the Rö point
avoid sitting and adjusting down and 1 so
should you shoot at shorter distances that is
so much fun too if you get to pick up stuff
everyone thinks it's fun to get putty
up his equipment Yes, but that's it
here we are testing some things
this one, for example, has some small
lamp
here I don't know if you see it but like when
you angle the gun if you shoot a little
further away then it is very sensitive